BRANDON KIARIE

+254 704873083 kiariebrandon24@gmail.com Milimani. Kitengela, Kajiado

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Dedicated software developer with experience in making web applications, building innovative tech projects and dedicated to continuous improvement to apply skills in software development. Reliable team member accustomed to taking on challenging tasks to produce top notch programming skills.

EXPERIENCE

STEM IMPACT CENTER KENYA, Upperhill, Nairobi — STEM TRAINER, WEB DEVELOPER

April 2022 - PRESENT

Embedded Systems Specialist using Arduino.

Robotics Trainer.

App Development trainer using HTML, CSS and Javascript creating custom websites and applications.

Web developer creating the 'STEM Shop' official website using HTML, CSS, Javascript and Laravel programming languages.

DAVIS CAKES, Kitengela, Kajiado — Web Developer

January 2023 - PRESENT

Website developer using HTML, CSS, Laravel and Javascript.

Website manager and technical advisor.

EDUCATION

Gearbox, Nairobi — Certificate January 2021 - August 2021 Certificate in Embedded Systems, Robotics.

Institute Of Software Technologies, Westlands, Nairobi — Diploma January 2022 - February 2023 Diploma in Software Development,

Software Engineering.

SKILLS

Creative ProblemSolving.

Interface Design.

Understanding of different programming languages.

Analytical Thinking. Software Development.

LANGUAGES

English, Fluent.

Swahili, Fluent.

DAVIS CAKES — Website

A user friendly website that allows all its users to be able to view and purchase cakes made at Davis Cakes Bakery. With an easy to checkout, the customers can choose to either pick up their orders or have it delivered to their chosen location. With a new feature called 'custom cake', customers can create their own designed cakes to meet their creative ideas.

The project was created using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Laravel programming languages.

STEM Shop — Web Application

Designing and developing a web application that users can browse through as they look for different robotics products. With the use of **Html**, **Css** and **JavaScript** as the main frontend programming languages I was able to create an interactive user interface. I integrated the project with **Laravel** as the main backend programming language so that the admin can view orders and also add and delete products

STEM BOOTCAMPS

In partnership with UNESCO and STEM Impact Center Kenya, we held STEM bootcamps in three Kenyan highschools. I trained young learners in Mobile app development and robotics using different programming languages. Different innovative projects were created that can impact positive change to our communities.